Guide to the Johan Kugelberg hip hop collection, circa 1975-1985, 2008.
Kugelberg, Johan hip hop collection,
- Series III. Party and Club Fliers (Box 32-37)
  - Oversized Fliers
    - Ecstasy Garage Disco, March 14, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Performers: Funky 4 plus 1 more: Keith-Keith, K-K Rockwell, Sha-Rock, Jazzy-Jay, Lil Rodney-C; Casanova Fly: Force 5 M.C.s: Lil Gee, Jerry D, Louie Lew, Butch Kid
      Event: N/A
      Price: M: $3 F:$2
    - Ecstasy Garage Disco, June 13, 1980; Also: 6/14/1980: Bambaataa (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Performers: Cold Crush: DJ Charlie Chase, DJ Tony Tone, Cold Crush 4 MC's; Chief Rocker Busy Bee Starsky; MC's Grandmaster Caz; Supreme Easy-A.D.; Jerry D. Lewis; Kay Gee; M.C. Starsky
      Flier creator: Sisco Kid
      Price: M: $3 F: $1 before 11, $2 after
    - Ecstasy Garage Disco, September 5, 1980; also 9/6/1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Performers: The Grand Wizard Theodore: Fantastic 5 M.C.s; Mean Gene; Fantasy 4 M.C.s; Starsky; Kool Dee
      Event: A Back To Scool Celebration!
      Price: M: $3, F: $2
    - Ecstasy Garage Disco, October 10, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Performers: D.J. Master Maze; Funkadelic II;Kid Supreme; Jazzy-O; Chiefrocker Starsky; Grandwizard Theodore: Fantastic V: Kevie Kev, Master Rob, Robbie Dee, Dot-la-Rock, Whipper Whip
      Flier creator: Nation
      Event promoter: Big IRV Production
      Price: M: $3, F: $2, $4 after 12
    - Ecstasy Garage Disco, December 28, 1980; 12/29/1980,12/30/1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Performers: 12/28 The Love Brothers: Mean Gene; Cordie-O; Theodore; MCs Master Rob, Kevie-Kev, Rubie-Dee 12/29 Dj Donald Dee & Co; Whipper Whip; Dota Rock 12/30 Afrika Bambaataa: DJ Jazzy Jay, MCs Hutch Hutch, Lisa Lee, Sundance, Pow Wow, Ice Ice, Mr. Biggs; Charley Chase
      Event: The Grand Opening of the Ecstasy Garage Disco
      Price: Free-$4
    - Harlem World, October 17, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Performers: Jimmy 'Super Rhymes' Splicer; Kurtis 'the Breaks' Blow; The Crash Crew: Mix Master Mike, Reggie Reg, Gee Man, Barry B-Stro, Disco Dave, Mike C., Lashubee, D.J. Darryl C.; [Special Added Attraction]: The Harlem World Crew; D.J. Hollywood: The Hollywood Corp; The Eddie Cheba Crew; Show Mc Reggie Wells
      Event: "In Concert Part II" A Birthday Celebration for Eddie Cheeba
      Event promoter: Cheeba/Godfather Production
      Price: $8 advance $10 door
    - N.A.A.C.P, May 4, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Performers: Touch of Class Disco; DJ Willie Will, DJ Disco Gee; DJ Mellow Beat; Nice and Nasty MCS: Terry Tee, Mexi Ray, Apollo One, Charlie D; Grandmaster Production: D.J. Commodore, D.J. Maestro, M.C. J.C., D.J. Scorpio, M.C. Timmy T., M.C. Bobby D.
      Event: A Disco Extravaganza
      Price: $2
    - N.A.A.C.P, May 4, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Performers: Grandmaster Production: D.J.S Courtney-Court, Mestro, Scorpio, Commodore, MC Timmy-T., MC J.C.; Touch of Class: D.J.s Mellow Beat, Willie Will, Disco-G.; Nice & Nasty 4 MC's: Mexy Ray, Apollo 1, Charlie- D., Terry-T.
      Event promoter: Idea Productions
    - N.A.A.C.P, November 23, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Performers: The Cheeba Crew: D.J. Kenny-Ken, D.J. Mighty-Mike; Awesome IV MC's: Sir-Rockwell, DJ Kevski, AJ-Rock, Little-Dee; Touch of Class: D.J.'s Mellow-Beat, Disco-Gee, Willy-will; Nice And Nasty MC's:Apollo-One, Mexi-Ray, Hi-Cee, Terry-Tee, Charlie-Dee
      Flier creator: Cool Cue
      Event promoter: Ghetto Children Productions
      Price: $2, $3 after midnight
    - P.A.L, January 19, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Performers: Spoonie-Gee; GranWizard Theodore; Kool Herc & Co.
      Flier creator: Brian Hicks, Anthony Riley
      Event: The Body Rock Festive of the Decade
      Event promoter: P.A.L. Productions 1980
      Price: $3 before 12, $4 after
    - P.A.L, December 25, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Performers: Brothers Disco: Baron, Breakout; KK Rockwell, Keith Keith, Sha Rock, Lil' Rodney C, Jazzy Jeff
      Event: A Birthday Disco Baasshhh for Alvita and No-No
      Price: $3 before 12
    - P.A.L, February 2, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Performers: Acey- Ace; B.B. Starski; Curtis Blow; Crotona Boys; Chuckie-Cee; Dota Dot; Donald-D; Easy "G"; Eve-A-Deaf; Kid Vicious; Tuff; Sherri-Sher; Whipper Whip; Funky4+1 More: KK Rockwell, Lil Rodney C, Sha-Rock, Jazzy-Jeff, KeithKeith; Chocolate Chip; RC; Mr.Hyde; Money Mike; Dr. Jekyll; Kenny-G; Tony "D"; Master E Man; Sweet -n- Sour; Sugar Hill Gang: B.B. Hank, Master G, Wonder Mike; The Furious 5: Mr. Ness, Raheim, Kidd Creole, Mele Mel, Cowboy; Tipsky; El-J; Smiley; Spoonie Gee; Scoopy; The Fantastic Trio: Kevie-Kev, Master Rob, Rubie-Dee; Soulsonic Force: Hutch Hutch, Ice ICe, Lisa Lee, Master B, Mr. Biggs, Pow Wow, Sundance, Master Ice; Dee Tee; Teddy-Ted; Lay-Lay; Zina-Z; Grand Master Flash; Grand Wizard Theodore
      Flier creator: Anthony Riley, Danny T.
      Event: The World Comes to the P.A.L. Em-Cee Convention
    - T-Connection, December 14, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Performers: The Cheeba Crew: D.J. Kenny-Ken, D.J. Mighty-Mike; The Awesome 4plus1: Sir Rockwell, A-J Rock, Kevski, Little Dee, Chocolate Chip; L. Brothers: DJ's Mean-Gene, Cordie-O, Theodore
      Price: $2 before 12 $3 after
    - T-Connection, March 21, 1980; phone number on back (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Performers: The Cold Crush Brothers: Dj Charlie Chase, Dj Tony Tone, Cutsologist Dee: ColdCrush IV M'Cs: Grandmaster Caz, Easy AD, K Gee, Jerry D. Lewis
      Price: M: $3 F: $2
    - T-Connection, June 21, 1980; 2 exact duplicates;one has notes for another flyer on back (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Performers: Grand Wizard Theodore: The Fantastic 5: Robbie Rob, Kevie Kev, Rubie Dee, Dota Rock, Whipper Whip; The Herculords; Jay Cee; Clark Kent; C.B. Crew; D.J love Squigg; The Devastating 4: Tricky Tee, Rob Ski, Mali Bu, Harry O; The Original Commodore 4: Willie Will, Baron B, Jerry D Lewis, Don Jaun; Fly Force Mc
      Flier creator: Herc
      Event: Get Up and Dance
      Price: $4 before 12 $5 after
    - T-Connection, July 12, 1980; phone number on back (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Performers: Grand Wizard Theodore: The Fantastic 5: Robbie Rob, Kevie Kev, Rubie Dee, Dota Rock, Whipper Whip; Chief Rocker Busy Bee Starsky; The Imperial JayCee; Touch of Class Disco; Nice & Nasty 4 M-C
      Event: Terrycloth Leisure Suit Disco
      Event promoter: T-Connection
      Price: M: $4 F: $3
    - T-Connection, October 15, 1982; also 10/16/1982; has a list of 70s dances (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Performers: 10/15 The "L" Brothers: Mean Gene, Theodore, Codio-O, Kev-E-Kev, Robbie Rob, Busy-Bee; The Zulu Nation: Bambaata, Jazzy Jay, Cosmic Force M.C.'s, D.J. Sinbad; The Herculoids: Kool Herc, Jay-Cee, Clark Kent, Sweet-N-Sour; Breakout: Breakout, Baron, Rodney-C, Raheim, K.K. Rockwell, Jazzy-Jeff, Sha-Rock; The Cold Crush Brothers: Charlie-Chase, Tony-Tone, EZ A.D., Whipper-Whip, Dot A Rock 10/16 Bambaataa: Cosmic Force M.C.'s, Soulsonic Force M.C.'s; Patti-Duke and the Jazzy 5 M.C.'s; Funky 4 Plus One; Rodney-C, Sha-Rock; K.K. Rockwell; D. J. Breakout; Keith-Keith; K.J. Baron; Jazzy-Jeff; Jazzy Dee
      Event: 10/15 A Tribute to the 70s 10/16 Oldies But Goodies Night
      Event promoter: 10/15 Hall of Fame/Richard T. 10/16 T-Connection Club, Richard T
      Price: $3-$4
    - La Cortorie Disco, June 23, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Performers: D.J. Baron, D.J. Breakout: The Funky 4 M.C.'s
      Event: A Salute to All 1978 Graduates
      Event promoter: The Brother's Disco
      Price: $3, $5couples
    - Ocean Village Beach/Village Disco, August 4, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Performers: D.J. Baron, D.J. Breakout: The Funky 4 M.C.'s: Sha Rock, Keith Keith, Raheem, K.K RockWell; We Wear Short Short Pants Disco
      Event: The First Annual Summer of...78 Beach Party
      Price: $7.50
    - P.S. 21 Park, May 27, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Performers: Fantasy MC Sweet K; Nasty Neal; Kool Kyle; J.J. Ronnie Ron; Mr. G.Q.;D.J. Steel; '78 Crew; The KRCO (?) Crew; Bronxwood Crew; The Freak Nation; Lil Bros.; Together Brothers; D.J. Way Way; The Old Sunrise Disco; Gunhill Crew; The Valley
      Event: Midnight Freak
      Event promoter: Creation and their Freak Nation (Creastion Disco)
      Price: Free
    - Bronx High School of Science, February 23, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      Performers: D.J. Baron, D.J. Breakout: The Funky 4 M.C.'s: Sha Rock, Keith Keith, Raheem, K.K RockWell
      Event promoter: Brothers Disco
      Price: $3
    - Lehman High School, March 23, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      Performers: Sunrise Disco: DJ's Pete, Tod
      Event: Holiday Disco Dance
      Price: $1advance $2door
    - Studio 125, October 5, 1979; also 10/7/1979 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      Performers: Grandmaster Flash: Disco Bee, Mele-Mel, Cowboy, Rahiem, Mr. Ness, Kid Creole; DJ Donald Dee and His Crew
      Flier creator: Danny T
      Event: Ladie's Night
      Price: F: Free before 12 M: $3
    - Club Three Seventy-One, November 21, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      Performers: First Choice; Three Seventy-One Crew; Eddie Cheeba
      Event: Another Super Bad Wednesday
      Event promoter: Warlock Productions in Association with James Harris Prouctions
      Price: $10
    - NY School of Printing, January 18, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      Performers: Grandmaster Flash: Disco Bee, E Z-Mike; Spoony Gee; D.J. A.J.; Busy Bee Starski; Magic Mike; The Five Shades of Black; D.J. Donald D.
      Event: Show Down of the Dee Jays Part II
      Event promoter: Disco Masters in association with Tiny Wood and Black Door Productions
      Price: M:$5 F:$4
    - Jr. High School 148, April 26, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      Performers: Cheeba Crew; D.J. Mean Gene; D.J. Mr. Ace; Grandwizard Theodore; MCs E-Z-Love; Vicious E; Bay-Bay B; Diamond T; DJ Wonder Woman; The Touch of Class and the Nice and Nasty MCs
      Flier creator: Diamond T
      Event promoter: Curtis H. Johnson
    - Player's Choice, May 16, 1980; list of invited high schools (Box 34, Folder 10)
      Performers: Reggie Wells; Eddie Cheeba; Disco Dave
      Flier creator: Sammy Tee
      Event: The Bronx is Up! Super Boss Sureshot Disco Show!! Talent&Fashion Show
      Event promoter: Tommie "L"
      Price: $5 flyer $6 no flyer
    - La-Sahute, October 3, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      Performers: Little Junior Soul; Georgette "GiGi" Rumph; G.T. Taylor; Mr. Showman Junior Soul; Martie Butler & The People's Heritage; M. C. Jean Harvie; Mr. Smoothie; Earl Moodie; D.J. Frankie
      Flier creator: Saccente's House of Printing
      Event: The Junior Soul 15th Anniversary Showcase
      Event promoter: Kingston Tropical Bakery, Inc. with James B. Kitchen and 2M Records
      Price: $12
    - 295 E. 206 St., December 6, 1980; writing on back: autograph practice by Curtis Sherrod and Russel Richardson (Box 34, Folder 10)
      Performers: DJ Whiz Kid; DJ Gordon; Mike G; Jazzy K
      Event: hip hop and don't stop jam
      Event promoter: J.J.D Productions
    - I.S. 201, January 31, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      Performers: Crash Crew: Gee-Man, Reggie Reg, EK Mike C, Darryl C, Barry B-Stro, La-Shu-Bee; Mr. Freeze: Cold Shocking 5; Crazy Eddie:OC Fearless 5; Bond and Elmo; Caz and Lewis; DJ Spivy, Kid Delight, Kool Ski; DJ Pernellio and Crew; Kool DJ AJ; Busy Bee Starski
      Event: The Great Disco War
      Event promoter: Mixmaster Mike, Disco Dave
      Price: $3 before 11
    - Walton High School, March 28, 1981; Two-sided (Box 34, Folder 11)
      Performers: The Kool D.J A.J. Show: Busy Bee Starsky, Ray-Von; Treacherous 3: Special K, L.A. Sunshine, Kool Moe D; Cold Crush Bros: Charlie Chase, Tony Tone: Coldcrush 4; Super 3 M.C.s: Mr. D, Renny D, Dave-sky
      Flier creator: Buddy Esquire, Martin Williams
      Event: A benefit for TAPCAPP BECONCERN Project
      Event promoter: Perry B. and Jazzy Wayne Productions
    - Community School 129, June 27, 1981; corner with price information missing; phone number scratched on back (Box 34, Folder 11)
      Performers: A Touch of Class Disco
      Event: Raffle and Disco
      Event promoter: Twin Parks Summer Day Camp
    - B&B Disco, November 6, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      Performers: The Factor 5: Slack, Ray-Rock, Harvey, DJ-Ski, Seville; DJ Hollywood; DJ Slide; Kid Kreel; DJ Breakout; Keith-Keith; Disco Four; Ca$h Money
      Event: A Galactic Showdown
      Event promoter: D.T.C Productions
      Price: M:$3 F:$2
    - Smith Projects, November 25, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      Performers: Brothers Disco: DJ Baron, DJ Breakout: The Funky 4 MCs: MC KK Rockwell, MC Keith Keith, MC Sha Rock, MC Raheim; Death Partner's Disco: DJ Doc-La-Rock, DJ One-Time: The 3 MCS: Kool Ice, Money Moe, Frank Nityyy; River Niles
      Flier creator: Kimani
      Event: Spank Contest
      Event promoter: Master Plan Productionnn
    - Sound Symposia, April 2, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      Performers: D.J. Mr. Bee; DJ Tony-T; Jazzy- K; Lil Man; Tiny-Tim; Elly-Gee
      Flier creator: Andyjam1
      Event: Dynamic-Disco
      Event promoter: Casa City Production
      Price: $2 flyer $3 no flyer
    - Hone's One Stop Record Distribution, N/A; Hot 60 Singles sold at their store (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - A.P. C Inc, N/A; Order sheet for Sugar Hill Gang memorabilia (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Bronx Boys Club (Hoe Ave.), December 23, 1981; 1 framed 11x17 flier (Box 44)
      Performers: Funky Four Plus One, DJ Breakout, Double Trouble
      Event promoter: Commencheros
  - Original Flyer Art (Box 36)
    - 3rd Ave Ballroom, February 16, 1979; Ink on paper, ruled pencil lines; signed on back 2/12/1979 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Performers: Brothers Disco Sisters Disco: D.J. Breakout D.J. Baron: The Funky Four M.C.s: Sha-Rock, Keith-Keith, Rahiem, K.K. Rockwell
      Event: 1979 Sweethearts Ball
      Price: $2, F free til 11
    - Columbus High School, March 16, 1979; Ink on paper, ruled pencil lines; signed on back 3/10/1980 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Performers: Brothers Disco Sisters Disco: D.J. Breakout D.J. Baron: The Funky Four M.C.s: Sha-Rock, Keith-Keith, Rahiem, K.K. Rockwell; TNT Disco; D.J.'s Shevy-Shev, Timmy Tim; The Jazzy 3 M.C.s
      Price: $2 tix $3 no tix
    - Fantasia, June 8, 1979; Ink on paper, ruled pencil lines; some original pencil writing; signed on back 6/1-2/1979 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Ecstasy Garage Disco, December 5, 1980; Words cut and pasted; border in ink; ruled pencil lines; signed on back 12/30-31/79 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      Performers: Touch of Class Disco: DJ's Mellow Beat, Disco Gee, Willy Will; Nice & Nasty M.C.S: Apollo-One, Mexi-Ray, Hi-Cee, Terry-Tee, Charlie-Dee
    - Ecstasy Garage Disco, February 22, 1980; Words cut and pasted-- "Buddy Esquire" yellow with black background; border in ink; ruled pencil lines; signed on back 2/14-15/80 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Performers: Grand Master Flash: Disco Bee E-Z Mike: Furious 5 M.C.s: Cowboy, Kid Creole, Mele-Mel, Mr. Ness, Rahiem;The Kool DJ A.J. Show: M.C's Chiefrocker Starsky, E-Man
      Event: An Album Giveaway
      Price: $4
    - 359th Armory, March 14, 1980; Ink on paper, ruled pencil lines; signed on back 3/11/1979; "3 M $16 due" (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Performers: Theodore: Fantastic 5 M.C.S: Kevie-Kev, Robie-Rob, Rubie-Dee, Dot-a-Rock, Whipper-Whip; Cold Crush Brothers: D.J.s Charlie-Chase, Tony-Tone, Kool-D, Grandmaster Caz, M.C.S E-Z A.D. K-Gee, Jerry-Dee;Players Disco: D.J.s D-Rock Nat-Skate, Mister-L: Fabulous 4 M.C.S.: Shaiem, Bill-Blass, Barry-D, Reggie-Reg; T.N.T Disco: D.J. Gary-G: The Jazzy 3 M.C.S: Gangster-Bee, Roger-K, Kid-Ice
    - P.A.L., May 23, 1980; Words cut and pasted; background in ink; ruled pencil lines; signed on back 5/17-18/80; "10AM Tues Paid" (Box 36, Folder 7)
      Performers: GrandMaster Flash: Furious 5 M.C.s: Mele-Mel, Mr. Ness, Rahiem, Cowboy, Kid Creole VS d.j. Breakout: Funky4plus1: Keith-Keith, K.K. Rockwell, Sha-Rock, Jazzy-Jeff, Lil Rodney-C; d.j. Darryl-C: The Force of the 5 MCS: Reggie-Reg, E-K-Mike-C, Barry-B, G-Man, La-Shu-Bee VS Act II Crew: d.j. Ronnie Green, Ray Von
      Event: The Battle of the Best
      Price: M:$4 F:$3
    - T. Neck Rec. Center, June 6, 1980; Words cut and pasted; background in ink; ruled pencil lines; signed on back 5/27/80 "2 M 4PM 22.00" (Box 36, Folder 8)
      Performers: The Grandmaster Flash Show: Grandmaster Flash, Disco Bee, E-Z Mike: Furious 5 M.C.s: Mele-Mel, Mr. Ness, Rahiem, Cowboy, Kid Creole; Act-II-Crew
      Price: $4 til 10
    - T-Connection, July 19, 1980; Words cut and pasted-- "Buddy Esquire" yellow with black background; border in ink; ruled pencil lines; signed on back 6/22/80; "White copies, please", notes about prices (Box 36, Folder 9)
      Performers: DJS Breakout, Baron: The Funky 4 plus 1 more: Keith-Keith, K.K.Rockwell, Sha-Rock, Jazzy-Jeff, Lil Rodney C
      Event: A Birthday Party for M.C. Jazzy Jeff
      Price: $2 til 10
    - T-Connection, August 23, 1980; Words cut and pasted; background in ink; ruled pencil lines; signed on back 8/14-15/80 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Ecstasy Garage Disco, August 28, 1980; Words cut and pasted-- Invited guests in yellow with black background; border in ink; ruled pencil lines; signed on back 8/18-19/80 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      Performers: Mean Gene: Fantasy 4 M.C.s, The Grand Wizard Theodore: Fantastic 5 M.C.s; [Invited Guests:] Starski, Bambaataa, G.M. Flash, Furious 5 M.C.s, Breakout, Baron Funk 4plus1, G.M. Caz; Jerry-D; Charley Chase; Cold Crush 4; The Herculords; Players Disco; Touch of Cass; Islam; Pete DJ Jones
      Event: A Thursday Night of Free Disco
    - Ecstasy Garage Disco, August 30, 1980; Words cut and pasted; background in ink; ruled pencil lines; signed on back 8/24-25/80 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      Performers: The Grand Wizard Theodore: Mean Gene, Kool Dee, Fantasy 4 M.C.s
      Event: A Citywide Convention Night
    - Ecstasy Garage Disco, September 12, 1980; Words cut and pasted; background in ink; ruled pencil lines; signed on back 9/4-5/80 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      Performers: The Notorious 2: Grand Master Caz, Jerry-D; Grand Wizard Theodore: Mean~Gene, Fantasy 5 M.C.S
      Price: M:$ 3 F:$2
    - Sons of Italy Ballroom, October 24, 1980; Words cut and pasted; background in ink; ruled pencil lines; rectangles outlined in pencil for photos; signed on back 10/12-13/80 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      Performers: The Grand Wizard Theodore Show: The Grand Wizard Theodore, Whiz-Kid, Grand Wiz Master; Master Scott; R.G. Kid; Bay-Bay B; Grandmaster Caz, Jerry D Lewis
      Price: $4 til 11, $5
    - Lemko Hall, October 31, 1980; Words cut and pasted; background in ink; ruled pencil lines; rectangles outlined in pencil for photos; signed on back 10/26-27/80 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      Performers: Crash Crew: d.j. Darryl-C: The Force of 5 M.C.s: Reggie-Reg, E-K-Mike-C, Barry-B, G-Man, La-Shu-Bee; The Grand Wizard Theodore: Fantastic 5 M.C.s: Kevie-Kev, Master Rob, Ruby-Dee, Dota-Rock, Whipper-Whip; Master Scott & R.G. Kid; Grandmaster Caz & Jerry D. Lewis; Bay-Bay-B; Players Disco
      Event: A Halloween Showdown
      Price: $5 til 11
    - T-Connection, December 12, 1980; Words cut and pasted; background in ink; ruled pencil lines; signed on back 12/8-9/80 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      Performers: Touch of Class Disco: DJS Mellow-Beat, Disco Gee, Willy-Will: Nice & Nasty 3: CharlieDee, Terry-Tee, Mexi-Ray; Crash Crew: d.j. Darryl-C: The Force of 5 M.C.s: Reggie-Reg, E-K-Mike-C, Barry-B, G-Man, La-Shu-Bee; Treacherous 3
    - Ecstasy Garage Disco, February 12, 1981; Words cut and pasted; background in ink; "Crew" colored in with blue pen; ruled pencil lines; signed on back 2/4-5/1981, Border dated 2/2/1980 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      Performers: Grandmaster Caz, Jerry D. Lewis; Mean-Gene:The Tantalizing 2; DJ Bucko & Crew
      Price: M:$2 F:$0
    - The Rollerdam Skating Rink, March 21, 1981; Words cut and pasted; background in ink; ruled pencil lines; signed on back 3/9-10/81 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      Performers: Touch of Class Disco: DJS Mellow-Beat, Disco Gee, Willy-Will: Nice & Nasty 3: CharlieDee, Terry-Tee, Mexi-Ray; [a tribute to:] Harlem World Crew, Lovebug Starski, Collins Bros., Bambaataa, Breakout & Baron, D.J. Hollywood, CrashCrew, D.S.T.
      Event: A Red Attire Night
    - Edenwald Center, December 11, 1981; Words cut and pasted; background in ink; ruled pencil lines; letters dated 12/8/8, background 12/9/81 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      Performers: dj Jazzy-Jay, dj Red Alert: Jazzy-5ive; [special guests:] Bambaataa, Lil Dave: Soulsonic & Comic Force M.C.S
      Event: Edenwald's 1st Bionic Boogie Jam
    - C-C-P-Rec, January 23, 1982; Words cut and pasted; background in ink; ruled pencil lines; signed 1/17/82, "Darrell, I want this back!" (Box 36, Folder 20)
      Performers: Cold Crush Brothers: Charlie Chase & Tony Tone: Cold Crush 4; Treacherous-Three; T-Ski Valley
      Event: A ColdCrush Birthday Jam for Kay Gee
    - River Park Towers, July 17, 1982; Words cut and pasted; background in ink--"Crew" in Blue letters; ruled pencil lines; letters dated 7/11/82, Pencil background 7/13/82, "fini" 7/14/82 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      Performers: Cutmaster Wiz Kid; Grandmaster Greg Gee; Chuck O' Luck; Force of the Tee MCs: Kool-E, Mean Machine, Eldorado Dee; Easy Tee; Kool Jay; Howard Bond; Bill Blast; Kool dj Clutch; Sugar Bear
      Event: Mid-summer Disco at the Tee
    - 777 E. 222 St., October 31, 1982; Words cut and pasted from colored paper, white paper; some from typewriter; some writing in ink; background in ink; on cardboard (Box 36, Folder 22)
      Performers: Touch of Class Disco: Nice and Nasty 3 M.C.s: Charlie-Dee, Mexi-Ray, Terry-Tee, DJ's Mellow Beat & Protege.Ike
      Flier creator: Curtis Sherrod
    - N/A, photograph with cut-outs: the heads and shoulders of the six performers are gone (Box 36, Folder 23)
      Performers: N/A
      Flier creator: photographer: Joey Kane
      Price: N/A
  - Buddy Esquire Flier Working Files (Box 37-39)
- Series IV. Textiles and original art (Box 42, 45)
  - Original art (Box 41)
  - Textiles (Box 42)
  - Tee shirts, tote bag (Box 45)
- Series V. Born in the Bronx
  - Page proofs for the book Born in the Bronx: a Visual Record of the Early Days of Hip Hop (Box 43)
  - Book release publicity (Box 40)
  - Documentation for Cornell University's October 31 - November 1 conference, Born in the Bronx (Box 35)
  - "Born in the Bronx" poster (Map-case Folder)
- Series VI. Miscellaneous
  - Manuscripts (Box 40)
  - 74 candid hip hop photos depicting various music events, record signings and performances - includes Raandu Avion, Brandy, Missy Elliott, Mary J. Blige, DMX and Wyclef Jean, 2001 (Box 35)
  - "Do the Right Thing" movie poster, 1989 (Map-case Folder)